(Howard:)Bernadette
and my mother are having
(Howard:)a get-to-know-you lunch
at the Old Town Deli.
(Raj:)Oh, that sounds lovely.
(Howard:)Hope so.
(Howard:)Of course, if history
is any indication,
(Howard:)my mother will swallow her whole
(Howard:)and spit out her bones
like an owl.
(Leonard:)Have you met
Bernadette's parents?
(Howard:)You mean Adolf and Eva?
(Howard:)Not yet.
(Howard:)One goose step at a time.
(Raj:)Sheldon,
that's my water.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord!
(Leonard:)That's not your water.
(Bernadette:)I know.
Where's the mouthwash?!
"Where" indeed.
(Howard:)Ma, I'm home!
(Howard:)Where are you?
I'm in the toilet!
So, how'd it go?!
Too soon to say!
I'm not done yet!
(Howard:)No, I mean lunch, today,
with Bernadette!